Special Operation Unit
Sergeant Kim Cheon-gyu
has passed away from the explosion.
The lead investigator, Min Gang-yong of
the Major Crimes Investigation Division,
was also severely injured and has been
transferred to a nearby hospital.
12 CASUALTIES IN GANGNAM HOTEL EXPLOSION
-Did you check the patient's vitals?
-I'm on my way.
LEE WOO-JEONG
WOO-JIN
Hello? Yes?
You're on a group call.
It's Woo-jeong. Are you there?
-Yes.
-I'm here, Woo-jeong.
Where are you both right now?
Mr. Moon brought me to a repair shop
that he knows well.
We have the girl
who drugged Min-beom with us.
Gun-woo, where are you?
Gang-yong got hurt. I'm at the hospital.
Gang-yong got hurt?
-Where is he?
-How? What happened?
Woo-jin, wait a minute.
Could you please hold for a moment?
-Yes.
-Gun-woo, how bad is everything?
Gang-yong,
he's being given a CT scan right now.
What condition is he in?
He's unresponsive.
-He's not responding.
-Shit! Fuck!
Then could you please stay where you are
and let me know if anything changes?
Will you do that for me?
Of course.
I'll head over to the repair
shop then. Woo-jin, give me the address.
I'll send it right away.
BLOODHOUNDS 2
Stay here.
Yes, of course.
When your father told me
what happened, I planned to see you.
I'm sorry I'm late.
What is it you need?
I need a specialist.
Is that what you want?
Yes. I need a person to be killed.
This the one who drugged you?
The one who ordered it.
Why were you drugged?
You did something?
I have an employee that cleans things.
I can put him on this one, but
think it over carefully.
If the guy deserves it.
I will return the favor any time.
All right.
The job will get done.
I'm thankful for this.
-Tell us! Who ordered the job?
-Oh, shut up!
Oh, fuck!
I've had enough.
I'm not in any mood for your games.
So tell me, who did it, huh?
Who ordered it?
Get close to me, okay?
Tell me.
Get closer.
This is stupid fucking shit.
Tell me! Who is it?
No, because it's a secret.
Hmm.
Hey, come on. Tell me the secret.
What?
Oh shit! Let go of him!
Oh fuck! What the hell?
You're fucking crazy!
Let me go.
No, don't do that. No.
Oh, whoa!
-Fucking let go of me! Let go!
-Control yourself.
Hold it together. Mr. Moon.
All right.
It's all right. It's okay.
Let go. I'm fine.
Having a laugh?
Yeah, it's so funny. It's so great.
Yeah, it's funny. It's so fun.
Oh, my stomach hurts.
Wow, young lady.
Look at you, with your pretty legs.
You must be popular.
But what if I break them?
It won't take much to break your knees.
They'll never heal
and you won't walk again.
Is that what you need?
Hmm?
I'm ready.
Please don't do that.
I'm so very frightened.
You won't do that, will you?
-I'm so very sorry. Please don't do that.
-So then just tell me. It's okay.
Please, go ahead. Tell me, who was it?
Stop crying. Just tell me.
"Just tell me."
You fucking idiot!
You're a fucking asshole.
-Stupid shithead.
-Fuck you!
-No! Don't let her get to you!
-Let go of me! She needs a lesson!
Fucking hell!
You're asking to get hurt.
You want to be punished?
Mm.
I like it very hard.
How will you punish me?
Fuck.
Hit me.
Do it. Go on, do it.
The guy said if I open up here
and say who paid for it,
then he will cut off my feet,
and sell me to be trafficked
in Southeast Asia.
You would keep your mouth shut too.
LEE WOO-JEONG
Woo-jeong. I'm here.
Are there any updates on the girl?
We threatened her,
but she's not saying anything to us.
She's a very tough one.
She almost bit Mr. Moon's ear off.
Did Mr. Moon do anything to her?
Not at all. No one hurt her.
No one touched her. We made threats.
So, is she the one who contacted Mr. Min
and gave him the info of the hotel?
Is that what happened?
No. Tae-yeong hacked her phone
and found it that way.
Ah.
Woo-jeong, could you then go inside
and maybe see her yourself?
Sure. Please tell me who she is.
Oh, come on. Just one cigarette.
You're all such fucking tight-asses!
All sorts of tactics. Damn it.
-Mr. Moon.
-Yes?
-Hello.
-Oh, you came.
Woo-jeong, welcome.
Well, I can't get through.
-You might be able to reason with her.
-Sure. I will try speaking with her.
Good luck.
Who said you could sit?
Fuck off, you disgusting ass!
Will you go fuck off?!
What's wrong with you?!
-Fuck this, seriously.
-Ah, don't do it!
Is it okay if I sit here?
Will you… work things out?
I'd appreciate it
if you could cooperate with us.
I can wait longer if you need.
Ah, this fucking sucks!
Who brought this guy?
Hey.
Just go fuck yourself already.
The police got info from your phone
and were able to raid the hotel.
Did you know that?
They probably think
you leaked the information
and they're looking for you right now.
You know how they'll hurt you.
They won't forgive you for the breach.
They'll never believe you,
no matter how much you try and explain.
They'll track you down
and they'll get their revenge.
So if you cooperate with us…
we can make sure you'll be safe.
How can you find a way
to protect me from them?
You see, if we catch them first, there'll
be no way for them to try and hurt you.
That'll be how we do it.
The next step would be a reduced sentence.
Are you fucking stupid
or out of your mind?
Why would I go to jail?
I have nothing to confess. Got it?
Gi-na? This is the deal.
If you cooperate with us…
we can help you
out of the situation safely.
Trust me.
Let me go.
The tape.
Sun-bo, you've got a knife?
Woo-jeong, think it through.
Thank you, Sun-bo.
The person who hired me is Lee Man-bae.
You know where he is now?
Why would I know that?
I only meet him when he has a job for me.
How long have you known him?
It's been three years
when he gave me the first job.
What did you do for him then?
Hey. For crying out loud,
why would I tell you?
Such a bitch.
Then can you say the names
of who Lee Man-bae's working with?
How would I know? I've met him once.
Why don't you give us some more
information about how he operates?
Hey, you there.
She has a lot of tactics.
A while ago,
we drank so much we blacked out.
That's when he told me he used to do work
for the National Intelligence Service.
But he left that job
because he had some troubles with money.
He couldn't find another job,
so he started connecting people
with the ones from the service.
He seemed honest about that.
But who knows for sure?
He's not exactly the open type.
You have his contact info?
It changes every time he calls.
He never answers when I call.
So we correspond via text, and I'd wait.
What was the drug
you put in Min-beom's drink?
Four-eyes.
Yeah?
Bring my bag here.
Will you help us meet with Lee Man-bae?
I'd get fucked then.
Gi-na.
We're in the same position.
You can only live if we catch them.
Oh, damn this to hell.
It's already so late. Tomorrow, I will.
Fine. We'll bring you to the hotel.
It's where we are.
Your place is too dangerous.
This way.
-Gun-woo, you're here?
-Hello.
When did you get back from the hospital?
Are you okay?
The doctor said I should go home.
How's Gang-yong?
He's still in the ER.
He's still unconscious.
So he's the same.
How are you? Did you get hurt? You okay?
You know,
I've been thinking about it.
I've thought it over.
I can't stop thinking…
that it's my fault.
That all of it's my fault.
No, it's not. It's not at all.
I should have just--
Gun-woo, listen to me, okay? Hey.
Just please hear me. Gun-woo.
Look at me. Okay? Hey, Kim Gun-woo.
Min-beom, Gang-yong, and Mr. Moon,
they were the ones who wanted to join us.
No matter what, they would have fought
with us anyway. You know that.
We couldn't have stopped them
from joining us,
and I understand why they've chosen to.
They've got to fight with us.
Why?
Because you did.
You risked your life
to fight for all of us.
We're connected because of you, Gun-woo.
You know that, right?
If you're gone from our lives,
it's like…
It's just not possible.
So if you're in danger or in trouble,
we all have to make sure to protect you.
Look at Gang-yong and Mr. Moon
for example.
A loan shark and a cop?
They don't really fit together,
and yet, it's working out.
Do you know why that is? Huh?
Gun-woo,
it's because of you…
that we're a family.
You're not the one causing problems.
You're keeping us alive.
It's all because of you that I'm here.
So, Gun-woo--
You know our rule, right?
Once a family…
A… always family.
And family?
Keep each other
s, s, safe…
…until we die.
Min-beom and Gang-yong will wake up soon.
They're really tough folks, you know.
So then,
you need to keep it together for them.
Understand?
Mm-hmm.
Feeling hungry?
Woo-jeong, are you hungry?
Let's order some room service.
Does a bunch of dishes, sound good?
Yeah, sounds great.
What should we order?
Woo-jin's right.
I'll protect.
I have to protect my family
with my own hands.
Hold on. This guy.
He's got a crazy long reach.
He'll do well against Gun-woo. Next.
Scroll down.
That one.
I want this fucker. He's a dirty fighter.
The exact opposite of Gun-woo.
Good shit. This'll be fun.
Hi, Tae-yeong. What is it?
You've got to see this.
It says this Thursday at 11 p.m.,
Gun-woo's going to fight.
When did you see this?
It was put up just right now.
Where's Gun-woo?
-He must have gone to exercise.
-They won't stop trying to get Gun-woo.
You have a linear fracture.
It's in the frontal bone area.
Can you see it?
Frontal bone?
This is a hairline fracture.
The hematoma
is causing intracranial pressure.
Until the pressure stops and returns
to normal, you need to get plenty of rest.
I get it. Thank you.
Wait, hold on.
There can be complications.
I realize the complications.
Thanks for your time.
We need to monitor it regularly.
Thanks again. Have a good day.
If the pressure increases,
you'll need surgery!
-There hasn't been a response yet?
-Nope.
Does Lee Man-bae normally
take a while to respond to you?
It always changes.
I want an iced coffee.
-Did you work out?
-Yeah, I went downstairs.
I could have gone with you.
You were sleeping deeply,
so I went by myself.
Then tomorrow,
we'll exercise together.
Mm.
GANG-YONG
Hello?
It's Gang-yong. Our champ, where are you?
You okay?
We've been all staying here at the hotel.
-Hey.
-Hello.
This way.
Please, over here.
Mr. Min!
Hi there. All right.
Mr. Min, you're fine?
You must be if you're out.
-I've got to keep it easy.
-Okay, good.
Don't worry.
Let's talk.
Yes.
Who could have told them
we were on our way?
I thought about every detective
and Special Operation Unit officers
who were at the scene.
I can't figure any of it out.
The dead are the only ones
who aren't suspects right now.
Maybe it was one of the hotel workers
I talked to.
Someone at the front desk when I called.
Then someone could have overheard
and leaked it.
Is this… what we need
to be focused on right now?
Mr. Min, it would be logical
to look at Lee Man-bae now.
We should move on our own.
Everyone wants to get us, so
we'll split up into two.
Woo-jeong and I will follow Lee Man-bae,
and Woo-jin and Gwang-mu will…
Oh, wait, I'm sorry.
No. Oh. No, my apologies.
Ah, it's all right.
You don't have to be too formal with me.
You both will handle
Yun Tae-geom's family.
-We have no idea when he might show up.
-Yes.
Mr. Min, we found the drug
used in President Hong's drink.
We sent it to Forensic Service.
Good. When will the results come out?
-The day after tomorrow.
-Great.
MARCH 13, 22:00
OLD BLDG. OF KOERI
Gun-woo.
-You okay?
-Yes?
Mr. Min wants to talk to you.
Yes, sir?
What do you wanna do?
What?
Uh, sir. Gun-woo can maybe stay here?
It could help
if he stays in this building.
Yes. The IKFC website had a post today
that said Gun-woo was going to be
having a fight there this Thursday night.
They'll do anything to get him to fight.
Since there's tight security,
this place will be the safest.
That's right. Yeah. It's for the best.
Stay here for a bit longer.
We'll catch them, no matter what.
Yes. Sir.
We're in this together.
Yes!
-Good. One, two, three.
-Let's do it!
Half. Call. Call, call.
Half. Call.
MANJI: WHERE ARE YOU?
Shit, fuck.
TARGET IN FRONT OF SOCIETY CAFE
ELIMINATE IMMEDIATELY
No! Shit!
Gi-na. Gi-na! Fuck.
-Look at me, Stay with us.
-Someone's been hurt!
674, Seoksan-dong, Jungang-gu.
Please hurry, please!
Just going for a short walk.
Follow me.
Sit down.
It's good to see you in person.
To think we could have done this sooner,
You stupid fucking asshole.
I lost billions because of you.
Anyway.
So tell me what makes you fight.
Family?
Friends?
Those aren't forever.
They'll leave in the end.
It's money that stays. It's what'll last.
Only the funds in your bank
are what protect you.
Money's what I fucking love.
Because money stays with you,
never betrays you.
Boxing was invented to make money.
That's why the same weight-classed
fighters are matched,
so they could last longer.
Better for television, for ads.
Boxers rest just enough
to stay alive for another one.
These rules… were all made
to make a lot of money.
So that's why
you're gonna make money too.
Got it?
I don't want money,
but let's do this.
Well done.
Then beat two assholes first.
And…
if you lose…
your whole family will die.
-Gun-woo!
-Gun-woo?
Anything wrong?
-We need to see Gun-woo.
-He just went out for a short walk.
He did?
GUN-WOO
Phone is turned off.
You will be connected to voicemail.
Wrap these on your knuckles.
This is how they fight here.
I'll keep fighting the way I do.
You won't win without these.
Ow!
The IKFC debut of the WBC
super middleweight champion begins.
Fighting out of Seoul, South Korea,
Kim "Scarface" Gun-woo!
His opponent, with an IKFC record
of seven wins and three losses,
Metal Mantis!
And let's blow this shit up!
Let's fight!
All right, the first fight has just begun.
Oh! Metal Mantis just landed
a sweet jab on his face.
Look at him. He's smiling.
He's literally enjoying this fight.
Whoa! Now it's getting wild now, yo.
They are throwing shots at each other
like there's no tomorrow.
Oh, look at him. Look at champ's
head movement. That is insane.
He's way too big, way too fast.
Ooh!
Uh-oh. What is he up to?
Ooh! Jeez, his footstep
is getting faster now.
It is getting faster, and faster.
What is he--
Oh!
Boom! Goddamn! He just knocked him out
with a fucking single shot!
-He takes the win! Let's go!
-They love him. It's insane.
They think Scarface…
He might be stronger than Hunter.
You see "KOERI"? Look it up.
Korea Ocean Engineering
Research Institute.
-Send officers there.
-Yes.
Let's fight!
Hey. Over here. It's game time.
All right.
All right, try and hit me!
I got you!
Shit! Shit.
Get down here!
-Put this asshole on the Intranet.
-Will do.
Let's fight!
Ugh!
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Agh!
Oh no! Poor Gun-woo!
Ay!
Agh!
Oh shit! We've got three minutes
to get out. The cops are here!
We've got to go now! The police!
President Im. We gotta go.
We have to leave now!
Let go, you little shithead!
Listen up. The cops are here. We gotta go!
-Doors are wedged!
-Bolt cutters!
I have them!
-I've got them.
-Run! Hurry!
-Get in there!
-Go in now! Hurry!
Grab them! Over there!
Hurry! Go faster!
We need an ambulance!
Woo-jin.
Gun-woo.
Hey, hey, be careful. Take it easy.
When did you get here?
Just about an hour ago.
How are you?
Mm.
Why'd you go there?
If I didn't show up, then…
they'd hurt Mom and you.
It could have been much worse.
I'm so sorry.
Why would you be sorry?
I'm very sorry.
Gun-woo, I already knew you did it for us.
That's who you are.
You protect others.
But, Gun-woo,
we always need to stick together.
That is what Mr. Choi told us.
From now on, let's stick together.
You got that?
If we die, we die together.
If we live, we live together.
That's who we are.
Im Baek-jeong was born in 1985.
He won a silver medal
in the light heavyweight division
at the Incheon Asian Games in 2014.
He turned pro and won 17 matches in a row.
He lost to the WBA
light heavyweight champion Chris Dustin.
He refused to accept the decision
and protested by assaulting the referee
and got physical with his coach.
He ended up serving time
for assaulting the referee
and was banned from the boxing association
when he disappeared.
Put a wanted alert.
Yes, sir. We will.
That was the most…
entertaining match so far.
The interesting thing is your fan base
is usually most excited
about the kind of fouls
that you don't see in mainstream fights,
but yesterday it wasn't the case.
Baek-jeong, you beautiful,
dirty son of a bitch,
when you fouled against Gun-woo,
the audience was up in arms.
I think we've found
the ultimate protagonist
that everyone wants to cheer for.
So I've decided to buy the IKFC
for $400 million.
51% shares, exactly.
However, I have two conditions.
First, a contract signed by Gun-woo to
fight three years exclusively in the IKFC.
Number two, you will lose to Gun-woo
in the next fight.
The IKFC doesn't need two shining stars.
Gun-woo's gonna be our new mascot,
and eventually, the face of the IKFC.
That means, Baek-jeong,
you're gonna have to step down.
Are you fucking kidding me?
This is my world.
I created the IKFC.
And that's why I'm paying you
and buying 51% of the shares.
I don't like it.
And one more thing.
What?
If I see you,
I'll kill you.
Go fuck yourself.
Yeah, fuck you, too, you fucking bastard!
What are you doing? He offered us
$400 million! This is what we want!
Ah!
Fucking asshole.
I'll do this my way. You stupid fuck.
You run your fucking mouth again
and you die, all right?
Okay. Yes, sir!
President Im.
The police have issued
a wanted alert for you.
What?
How'd that happen?
You'll need to leave.
You've got to get out of Korea.
I can arrange it. A jet just for you.
Oh, shit's fucking…
-Get me Gun-woo's mom
-What?
If I have her,
that asshole will listen and follow!
This time, it'll be to the death.
'Cause only one of us is going down.
Those fucking bastards!
I'll show them who the real deal is.
I'll turn it all upside down.